<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>TWR</title>
    <link>https://technicalwriterresources.pages.dev/</link>
    <description>Recent content on TWR</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2022, Wisdom Nwokocha all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://technicalwriterresources.pages.dev/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Content producer @Non Fungible Labs</title>
      <link>https://technicalwriterresources.pages.dev/post/nonfungible/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technicalwriterresources.pages.dev/post/nonfungible/</guid>
      <description>Title: Content producer
Job Location: Remote
Level: Senior
We are looking for a creative Content Producer to help us in the creation of an engaging and compelling podcast. As Content Producer, you will have the freedom to use your imagination and independent professional judgment in writing, producing, interviewing, taping, and broadcasting on-air content. This is a chance to build the podcast initiative from the ground up and make it the number one podcast on the new and ever evolving space of the metaverse and NFTs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Content Writer @VenturePunk</title>
      <link>https://technicalwriterresources.pages.dev/post/venturepunk/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technicalwriterresources.pages.dev/post/venturepunk/</guid>
      <description>Job Location: Remote
Level: Senior
We’re hiring a founding Content Creator @ VenturePunk, an early-stage web3 product studio. It’s a unique opportunity to work with a proven founder and get on the ground floor of a seed-stage startup building multiple projects in crypto, NFTs, and the metaverse. This role is fully remote.
Apply
Subscribe to my newsletter for more jobs and writing tips in your email
Subscribe here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Technical Writer @Adyen</title>
      <link>https://technicalwriterresources.pages.dev/post/adyen/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technicalwriterresources.pages.dev/post/adyen/</guid>
      <description>Title: Technical Writer
Job Location: Remote
Level: Senior
Do you enjoy working on the nitty gritty, but also looking at the bigger picture? Do you love to break down complex text into easy to understand content? Are you able to shift focus and tone according to different audiences?
Due to the growth of the company we are looking for multiple Technical Writers to join the team who understand the technical details and can write documentation for developers interested in integrating with our APIs or SDKs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Technical Writer @Terra</title>
      <link>https://technicalwriterresources.pages.dev/post/terra/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technicalwriterresources.pages.dev/post/terra/</guid>
      <description>Job Location: Remote
Level: Senior
At its core, Terra is a platform for developers. Developers can build applications on top of the Terra blockchain for countless use cases in crypto.
Apply
Subscribe to my newsletter for more jobs and writing tips in your email
Subscribe here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Technical Writer @MongoDb Realm</title>
      <link>https://technicalwriterresources.pages.dev/post/realm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technicalwriterresources.pages.dev/post/realm/</guid>
      <description>Job Location: Remote
Level: Senior
The Documentation team is a hands-on and enthusiastic group of engineers who are passionate about teaching developers how to work with data and build applications. We are hiring a Technical Writer to help us create world-class educational content for MongoDB&amp;rsquo;s developer-focused products &amp;ndash; in particular, Atlas App Services, Realm (mobile database), and Atlas Device Sync.
Apply
Subscribe to my newsletter for more jobs and writing tips in your email</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Technical Writer @Platform.sh</title>
      <link>https://technicalwriterresources.pages.dev/post/platformsh/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technicalwriterresources.pages.dev/post/platformsh/</guid>
      <description>Title: Senior Technical Writer
The Technical Writing &amp;amp; Education team is looking for a Senior Technical Writer to help with our public documentation. The job involves organizing, updating, and optimizing the materials we have to help developers use Platform.sh. The role reports to the Technical Education Manager.
The hours for the role are flexible, but should ideally have at least some overlap with CET.
Job Location: Remote
Level: Senior
Apply</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Communities</title>
      <link>https://technicalwriterresources.pages.dev/communities/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technicalwriterresources.pages.dev/communities/</guid>
      <description>What is a writing community A writing community act as the perfect support system for writers who want to stay updated with all the latest trends in technology. They help them hone their skills, share knowledge, collaborate on projects, get mentorship, and interact with others in the field who share the same passion.
Why do you want to join a tech community? Engaging with the community provides the perfect opportunity to network, collaborate, and innovate with individuals that share the same interests as you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Event</title>
      <link>https://technicalwriterresources.pages.dev/event/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technicalwriterresources.pages.dev/event/</guid>
      <description>Technical writing tips for a successful interview
Date: 30th July 2022
Time: 8PM GMT+1</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Freelance jobs</title>
      <link>https://technicalwriterresources.pages.dev/freelance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technicalwriterresources.pages.dev/freelance/</guid>
      <description>3di Information Solutions Ltd They are looking for freelance technical writers with experience creating documentation for the electrical engineering industry. They will like to hear from freelancers who are available to start immediately and have 25+ hours a week for at least 12 weeks.
Appsmith $200-$400 per article Topics that excite us are internal tools, low code, open-source, databases, application performance, engineering best practices, Javascript. And needless to say, newer ways to use Appsmith.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources for writers</title>
      <link>https://technicalwriterresources.pages.dev/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technicalwriterresources.pages.dev/resources/</guid>
      <description>This video will teach you how to build a technical writing project on github.
Nine Best Writing Tools In this article, I will list nine awesome writing tools that will make you a better writer. The tools were built to help writers be productive and care more about the details than finding typos and punctuation errors.
Contentre Contentre helps technical writers organize all their technical contents in one place, create multiple personalized portfolios,gain more clients and grow their technical writing career in one place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://technicalwriterresources.pages.dev/archives/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technicalwriterresources.pages.dev/archives/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://technicalwriterresources.pages.dev/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technicalwriterresources.pages.dev/about/</guid>
      <description>Nwokocha Wisdom Maduabuchi Senior Technical Writer
A passionate and highly organized, innovative Open source Technical Documentation Engineer with 3+ years of experience crafting both internal and user-facing support/learning documentation. Leverages background in computer science to write for highly technical audiences and also a Documentation static site engineer(Eleventy, Docsify, MkDocs, Hugo, DITA, Asciidoc, Open Api Spec) and (Confluence, Gitbook, Readme.io), Software / Blockchain(Solidity smart contract) Engineer.
You can reach me via</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
