<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on TWR</title>
    <link>https://technicalwriterresources.pages.dev/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on TWR</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2022, Wisdom Nwokocha all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://technicalwriterresources.pages.dev/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Introduction To Technical Writer</title>
      <link>https://technicalwriterresources.pages.dev/post/intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technicalwriterresources.pages.dev/post/intro/</guid>
      <description>Introduction to technical writing Socials:
LinkedIn Twitter Technical writing is writing about any technical issue, rather than a specialized technical topic such as computers. According to the Cambridge dictionary (The phrase &amp;ldquo;technical&amp;rdquo; refers to involving or needing special skills or knowledge ), which is the domain of experts and specialists. Whatever your major, you&amp;rsquo;re honing your skills and becoming a specialist in a certain technical field. And you&amp;rsquo;re engaging in technical communication whenever you try to write or speak about your field.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Use Of English</title>
      <link>https://technicalwriterresources.pages.dev/post/useofenglish/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technicalwriterresources.pages.dev/post/useofenglish/</guid>
      <description>Parts of speech
Sentence structure Guidelines for structuring ideas in a sentence Active and passive voice Concord Punctuation Technical writing is an aspect of English for Specific Purposes (ESP). In ESP, English is taught to suit the specific needs of diverse professions, occupations or activities. Now, technical writing is a form of writing that documents information about different specialties such as medical practice, computer and software engineering, technology, social science and so on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great Documentation</title>
      <link>https://technicalwriterresources.pages.dev/post/great-documentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technicalwriterresources.pages.dev/post/great-documentation/</guid>
      <description>Why is great documentation important? Important for scalability — first line of defense against the tsunami of user questions
Great marketing tool – great documentation helps attract and sustain communities
Reflection on the quality of the product. Poor and lazy documentation = poor quality product
What makes great documentation? Detailed. Answers any questions the user might be thinking.
Well organized (specific articles for specific purposes)
Well-written (proper grammar, spelling, and punctuation)</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
