<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on TWR</title>
    <link>https://technicalwriterresources.pages.dev/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on TWR</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2022, Wisdom Nwokocha all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://technicalwriterresources.pages.dev/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Content producer @Non Fungible Labs</title>
      <link>https://technicalwriterresources.pages.dev/post/nonfungible/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technicalwriterresources.pages.dev/post/nonfungible/</guid>
      <description>Title: Content producer
Job Location: Remote
Level: Senior
We are looking for a creative Content Producer to help us in the creation of an engaging and compelling podcast. As Content Producer, you will have the freedom to use your imagination and independent professional judgment in writing, producing, interviewing, taping, and broadcasting on-air content. This is a chance to build the podcast initiative from the ground up and make it the number one podcast on the new and ever evolving space of the metaverse and NFTs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Content Writer @VenturePunk</title>
      <link>https://technicalwriterresources.pages.dev/post/venturepunk/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technicalwriterresources.pages.dev/post/venturepunk/</guid>
      <description>Job Location: Remote
Level: Senior
We’re hiring a founding Content Creator @ VenturePunk, an early-stage web3 product studio. It’s a unique opportunity to work with a proven founder and get on the ground floor of a seed-stage startup building multiple projects in crypto, NFTs, and the metaverse. This role is fully remote.
Apply
Subscribe to my newsletter for more jobs and writing tips in your email
Subscribe here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Technical Writer @Adyen</title>
      <link>https://technicalwriterresources.pages.dev/post/adyen/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technicalwriterresources.pages.dev/post/adyen/</guid>
      <description>Title: Technical Writer
Job Location: Remote
Level: Senior
Do you enjoy working on the nitty gritty, but also looking at the bigger picture? Do you love to break down complex text into easy to understand content? Are you able to shift focus and tone according to different audiences?
Due to the growth of the company we are looking for multiple Technical Writers to join the team who understand the technical details and can write documentation for developers interested in integrating with our APIs or SDKs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Technical Writer @Terra</title>
      <link>https://technicalwriterresources.pages.dev/post/terra/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technicalwriterresources.pages.dev/post/terra/</guid>
      <description>Job Location: Remote
Level: Senior
At its core, Terra is a platform for developers. Developers can build applications on top of the Terra blockchain for countless use cases in crypto.
Apply
Subscribe to my newsletter for more jobs and writing tips in your email
Subscribe here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Technical Writer @MongoDb Realm</title>
      <link>https://technicalwriterresources.pages.dev/post/realm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technicalwriterresources.pages.dev/post/realm/</guid>
      <description>Job Location: Remote
Level: Senior
The Documentation team is a hands-on and enthusiastic group of engineers who are passionate about teaching developers how to work with data and build applications. We are hiring a Technical Writer to help us create world-class educational content for MongoDB&amp;rsquo;s developer-focused products &amp;ndash; in particular, Atlas App Services, Realm (mobile database), and Atlas Device Sync.
Apply
Subscribe to my newsletter for more jobs and writing tips in your email</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Technical Writer @Platform.sh</title>
      <link>https://technicalwriterresources.pages.dev/post/platformsh/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technicalwriterresources.pages.dev/post/platformsh/</guid>
      <description>Title: Senior Technical Writer
The Technical Writing &amp;amp; Education team is looking for a Senior Technical Writer to help with our public documentation. The job involves organizing, updating, and optimizing the materials we have to help developers use Platform.sh. The role reports to the Technical Education Manager.
The hours for the role are flexible, but should ideally have at least some overlap with CET.
Job Location: Remote
Level: Senior
Apply</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
