<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on TWR</title>
    <link>https://technicalwriterresources.pages.dev/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on TWR</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2022, Wisdom Nwokocha all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://technicalwriterresources.pages.dev/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to doc as code</title>
      <link>https://technicalwriterresources.pages.dev/post/introduction-to-doc-as-code/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technicalwriterresources.pages.dev/post/introduction-to-doc-as-code/</guid>
      <description>Writing, revising, and publishing procedures can be made more efficient using the documentation technique and practice known as &amp;ldquo;docs as code.&amp;rdquo;
Docs as Code, as the name suggests, handles all documentation like a codebase. Docs as Code recommends writing in a plaintext markup language like Markdown, pushing that documentation through an automated pipeline that tests the quality of the writing, and ultimately building and publishing the documentation to the public.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Web development </title>
      <link>https://technicalwriterresources.pages.dev/post/introduction-to-web-development/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technicalwriterresources.pages.dev/post/introduction-to-web-development/</guid>
      <description>Web development is the work involved in developing a website for the Internet or an intranet. Web development can range from developing a simple single static page of plain text to complex web applications. Before you can become a web developer, or start building those application, you need to understand the basics and fundamentals of web development.
You can read through the complete beginner guide to web development on MDN</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Subject Matter Expert</title>
      <link>https://technicalwriterresources.pages.dev/post/subjectmatterexpert/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technicalwriterresources.pages.dev/post/subjectmatterexpert/</guid>
      <description> Discussion How I got into technical writing Who are subject matter experts Why do they matter Subject matter experts as a best practice in technical writing Tell a story My journey into technical writing Loved writing as a child Traditional copywriter Followed my curiosity with technology Specialization Web3 needs strong communicators for adoption Who qualifies as a subject matter expert People with first-hand experience People building the technology you’re writing about: engineers, founders, developers, CTOs Academics: people versed in theory and history End-users: people using the technology you’re writing about Why do they matter Misinformation and fake news Clickbait Vaporware Scams Best practise Show don’t tell Direct quotes Paraphrase, cite, attribute Establish rapport and trust </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to KnowledgeBase </title>
      <link>https://technicalwriterresources.pages.dev/post/introduction-to-knowledgebase/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technicalwriterresources.pages.dev/post/introduction-to-knowledgebase/</guid>
      <description> Agenda This deck covers the following topics:
User Guides Troubleshooting Guides Installation Guides Integration Guides White-papers Knowledge base Importance of Technical Writing Drives the technical vision and attention on knowledge. Maps the information for any organization. Aligns processes with information. Brings up front the value of the resources. Highlights the obvious. Layers data based on history and evolution. Case Study- Stripe- What- https://stripe.com/docs How- https://support.stripe.com/ Where- https://stripe.com/docs/products </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Style Guide</title>
      <link>https://technicalwriterresources.pages.dev/post/style-guide-collection/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technicalwriterresources.pages.dev/post/style-guide-collection/</guid>
      <description>Style guides Submitted by https://github.com/barriebyron for the September 2022 mentoring program hosted by Wisdom.
I’m a word nerd and I love style guides. Learn more about me https://linktr.ee/barriebyron.
In my daily work as a technical communicator, I don&amp;rsquo;t have to remember everything. Instead, I just remember where to look for the answers to my many questions. I rely on trusted style guides.
I bookmark frequently visited pages in style guides on my web browser at work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Markdown </title>
      <link>https://technicalwriterresources.pages.dev/post/introduction-to-markdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technicalwriterresources.pages.dev/post/introduction-to-markdown/</guid>
      <description>Markdown is a lightweight markup language that can be used to format plaintext text documents. It was created by John Gruber in 2004, it is now one of the world’s most popular markup languages.
Markdown is not the same as using a WYSIWYG editor. To format words in an application like Microsoft Word, you click buttons, and the changes are immediately visible. Markdown does not work like that. When you create a Markdown-formatted file, you use Markdown syntax to indicate which words and phrases should be formatted differently.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Git Essential Training - The Basics</title>
      <link>https://technicalwriterresources.pages.dev/post/git-essential-basics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technicalwriterresources.pages.dev/post/git-essential-basics/</guid>
      <description>Git Essential Training: The Basics What is Git? Git is a software that allows you to: Keeps track of changes you make to your files and directories, it also keeps track of text changes. Git allows you to keep track of versions of your documents, it allows you to move back and forth between the versions of your document. The primary purpose of all version control systems is to manage source codes, this enables developers to manage the different versions of their codebase as they continue to add features.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Command Line Interface </title>
      <link>https://technicalwriterresources.pages.dev/post/commandline-interface/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technicalwriterresources.pages.dev/post/commandline-interface/</guid>
      <description>Windows has a shell OS which is CMD.EXE and Powershell. However, some linux command does not work on the windows command line. The windows powershell and CMD has different commands (and some of the same) with Bash, Zsh and other Unix-based shells. Thankfully, there are some Unix-based solution for windows, some of the most popular one’s are the Git-bash and WSL (Windows Subsystem for Linux). You can download and install any of them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Information Architecture and Topic-based writing </title>
      <link>https://technicalwriterresources.pages.dev/post/informationarchitecture/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technicalwriterresources.pages.dev/post/informationarchitecture/</guid>
      <description>Information architecture is arranging your information to ensure usability, readability, and information flow. Best way to ensure implementation of information architecture is arranging information logically, using self-explanatory headings.
Arranging information on the basis type of content brings us to topic-based writing. A topic is an independent chunk of information that covers a single idea or task. Any information that you write can be grouped in to one of the following topic types:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction To Technical Writer</title>
      <link>https://technicalwriterresources.pages.dev/post/intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technicalwriterresources.pages.dev/post/intro/</guid>
      <description>Introduction to technical writing Socials:
LinkedIn Twitter Technical writing is writing about any technical issue, rather than a specialized technical topic such as computers. According to the Cambridge dictionary (The phrase &amp;ldquo;technical&amp;rdquo; refers to involving or needing special skills or knowledge ), which is the domain of experts and specialists. Whatever your major, you&amp;rsquo;re honing your skills and becoming a specialist in a certain technical field. And you&amp;rsquo;re engaging in technical communication whenever you try to write or speak about your field.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Use Of English</title>
      <link>https://technicalwriterresources.pages.dev/post/useofenglish/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technicalwriterresources.pages.dev/post/useofenglish/</guid>
      <description>Parts of speech
Sentence structure Guidelines for structuring ideas in a sentence Active and passive voice Concord Punctuation Technical writing is an aspect of English for Specific Purposes (ESP). In ESP, English is taught to suit the specific needs of diverse professions, occupations or activities. Now, technical writing is a form of writing that documents information about different specialties such as medical practice, computer and software engineering, technology, social science and so on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great Documentation</title>
      <link>https://technicalwriterresources.pages.dev/post/great-documentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technicalwriterresources.pages.dev/post/great-documentation/</guid>
      <description>Why is great documentation important? Important for scalability — first line of defense against the tsunami of user questions
Great marketing tool – great documentation helps attract and sustain communities
Reflection on the quality of the product. Poor and lazy documentation = poor quality product
What makes great documentation? Detailed. Answers any questions the user might be thinking.
Well organized (specific articles for specific purposes)
Well-written (proper grammar, spelling, and punctuation)</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
